academicpositions.com 2016-10-25

# Privacy Policy - TASL - TASL Web Application

Search

  * Public Classes
  * Conferences
  * Custom Classes
  * Organizations
  * AcademicPositions
  * Products
  * Services
  * Venues

Information
  * About us
  * Accolades
  * Contact Us

| 

TASL's Privacy Policy

Version 06/01/2006

**TASL** is committed to protecting your privacy. We gather information to make your search, registration, and order experiences as convenient and successful as possible. We maintain the privacy of your information using security technologies and adhere to policies that prevent unauthorized use. 

##### Registration and Orders

  * Event registration and product ordering at our site is optional. To complete a registration or order we ask you to provide your name, organization if any, e-mail address, physical address, telephone number, and credit card number and expiration date, and this information is required in order to complete your registration or order. We share the contact information you provide with the provider of the specific event or product in order to complete your registration or order. And we may use it, at your option, to notify you of improvements to our site, upcoming events, or product specials. We use your financial information to bill your credit card for your registration or order. At your option, we may store it on our secure server, to save you time on future registrations and orders. We also offer you the option of registering or ordering by telephone (by calling 800-735-8275 within the U.S. or 925-735-8275 from outside the U.S.). 

##### Site Usage Information.

  * We track site usage to help us continuously improve our site�s relevance and ease of use, and may also use this information to inform you of site improvements, new features, upcoming events, and specials.

##### Other Information Requests.

  * Any additional information we may request is optional, and is requested to help us better understand your needs so that we can continuously improve your results and overall experience at our site. 

##### Information Provided to 3rd Parties.

  * Outside the process of sharing your contact information with the event or product provider in order to complete a specific registration or order, we do not share your individual information with any third party. **We do not sell our mailing list**. If the TASL site is co-branded with another entity, we may share aggregate information, without personal details, about site usage and traffic patterns with the co-branded partner.

##### Cookies.

  * Cookies are a feature of your Internet browser that allows information you enter in a web-site to be carried through that site for easy access. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. These files allow you to easily access your customer data on a web site, providing continuity and convenience. Cookies typically only carry information that you have previously entered and have no inherent capacity to track or collect other information. TASL will not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless you have knowingly provided such information.

##### TASL Privacy Policy Changes.

  * Any changes in our privacy policy will always be posted here before going into effect. 

##### Questions.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at:  
TASL, Inc.  
San Ramon, California   
Telephone: +1-510-537-7863  
E-mail: [support@tasl.com](mailto:support@tasl.com)
